Nate Worley

Computer Science Student/Graphic Designer

Email: nate.worley12@gmail.com | Cell: 469-406-9156 | Address: 2101 Bishop Barrel Ln, Wylie, TX 75098

Website: https://nateworley12.wixsite.com/mythz | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nathaniel-worley-a21030150/

SUMMARY

My name is Nate Worley and I currently work as a professional car photographer in Dallas, TX. I have a huge passion for computers and a love for innovation and creating. I am currently attending DeVry University for a bachelors in Software Engineering and am enrolled in SMU's Coding Bootcamp. I have been working as a professional photographer for 3 years and have been creating graphics professionally for 5 years. I have a very strong background and knowledge in Microsoft applications and Adobe products among other design programs to create any graphic or design need. I believe that this has well equipped me with the experience and skills needed to succeed in the tech and design industry. I have a strong desire to learn and have a very high learning agility. I believe this makes me an invaluable asset to any business or organization coupled with my experience in the customer service field as a manager, honed communication skills and leadership ability. With great personal drive, learning agility, a passion for computers and creating, I believe that I'm more than ready to turn my passions into a fulfilling career.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Manager| 08/2014 - 11/2016 Kroger | Wylie, TX

Time Management • Leadership • Communication

- · Leading and managing a department of front end employees / Scheduling Breaks
- Maintaining a well stocked store front / Ordering Workplace Materials
- Ability to exceed and company goals / Meeting Metrics

Licensed Claims Adjuster | 11/2016 - 10/2017 State Farm | Richardson, TX

Critical Thinking • Customer Service • Professionalism

- Accessing damages and sending money for customers repairs / Writing Checks for Damages
- Taking phone calls from customers and solving their situations / Effective Communication
- Resolving legal faults for insurance claims / Situational Problem Solving

Car Photographer | 10/2017 - 10/2018, 07/2019 - 12/2019 AutoCartel | SouthLake, TX

Creativity • Adobe Applications • Learning Agility

- · Providing the consumer with satisfactory pictures / Consumer Satisfaction
- · Ability to stay ahead of the photography curve / Commercial and Cultural Awareness
- · Managing time to provide consistent content and services / Meeting Deadlines

Graphic Designer | 12/2019 - Present Infinite Electronics | Lewisville, TX

Creativity • Adobe Applications • Time Management

- · Maintaining nine different brands and their different styles / Diligence
- · Ability to stay ahead of the Graphic Design curve / Commercial and Cultural Awareness
- Managing time to provide consistent content and services / Meeting Deadlines

EDUCATION

High School Diploma | 06/2015 Wylie High School | Wylie, TX

GPA: 3.6

BS - Software Engineering | Currently Attending DeVry University |

- · Current GPA: 3.8
- **SMU Coding Bootcamp**| Currently Attending Southern Methodist Dallas, TX

SKILLS

Personal Management | Learning Agility | Marketing Skills

Microsoft Applications | Innovation | Teamwork

Leadership Ability | Communication | Drive

CODING SKILLS

HTML | CSS | JavaScript

Node.js | Python

ADDITIONAL CREATIVE MEDIA WORK

- Stock Photographer For Shutterstock
- Esport Event Photography
- Photography and Graphics For Northplace Church
- Ads, Logos And Brand Graphics For Businesses
- Graphics, Ads and Logos for Wylie High School
- Real Estate Photography

ADDITIONAL CODING WORK

- GitHub | https://github.com/ImMythz
- Portfolio | https://immythz.github.io/Professional_Portfolio/

REFERENCES

These are available upon request